{
    "id": "ed4eb80bd2694d16a0e8922d36e9cbb9",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One day man will ……………….. colonize Mars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "be able to",
                "been able to",
                "have been able to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20903705b21142c996ec8f0a636f9cb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "What have you ....................... to find out?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "able",
                "been able",
                "were able"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7694c803149e4dafbd9c49b2dfcba8d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very much interested in ..................... to paint.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to learn",
                "learning",
                "to learning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "88c641c08e304036b20391c4c696238b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t look happy .....................… me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "in seeing",
                "at seeing",
                "to seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3247ce035be4c02955d3c2cd0e131c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "That dress is new, .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "has it"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0490c18c27c048288f58a7f9618b6e65"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was .....................… that I didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a so warm day",
                "so warm a day",
                "so warm day"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fac1d0ec6a64c07948df96fd3b2172c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ....................... in love with each other, so everybody was surprised when they decided to part ways.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mad",
                "madly",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52517cce3cd24f3393ac1ddd3d471253"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was .....................… injured in the crash.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fatal",
                "fatally",
                "dead",
                "deadly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54a6da493e8c432fa59483b596063e96"
        },
        {
            "question": "Feel ……………….. to speak. I won’t tell anyone what you say.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "free",
                "freely",
                "with freedom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1069974d4ee42c989e034b81dc8c293"
        },
        {
            "question": "I very much enjoy ..................... ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to read",
                "reading",
                "to reading"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d229562436c4472584d2397d693f03e9"
        }
    ]
}